Today something happened at our house that left all of us in such a state.
[laughs]
I was sitting so worried since this morning, then
Rama comes running to me and
says, Mom, what happened to you?  Why are you crying
?
So I had ordered some stuff for myself
and that stuff is going to be delivered at home tomorrow
and now I did not have a single penny to pay.
And on hearing this, Rama runs away.
And after some time Rama comes to me and says,
Mummy, take Papa's parts.
You can withdraw as much money as you want from these.  And now
brother, there is no need for me to cry.  Now
I have so much money.  And then the next
morning I ordered all my stuff with this same money.
And now come quickly, let me hide all this stuff.
Otherwise my husband will
come home and shout at me unnecessarily.
[Music]
Hey, what happened?
And today, ever since my husband came home, I do
n't know what happened to him?  So I
asked, hey, what happened?  Why are you acting like a mad person
?
All the money I had disappeared.
Hey, you could have asked me.  I had
taken the money.  This means that if I had asked you to
take the money, you would not have given it to me.  Ok.  Don't
come inside the house after today.